{
    "translations": {
      "en": {
        "1": {
          "type": "select",
          "description": "",
          "question": "What is the Value of this index?",
          "answer": "3",
          "choices": ["3", "-8", "-7"]
        },
        "2": {
          "type": "select",
          "description": "",
          "question": "What is the Value of this index?",
          "answer": "-1",
          "choices": ["-12", "-8", "-1"]
        },
        "3": {
          "type": "select",
          "description": "",
          "question": "What is the Value of this index?",
          "answer": "-5",
          "choices": ["-5", "-10", "-12"]
        },
        "4": {
          "type": "select",
          "description": "",
          "question": "What is the Value of this index?",
          "answer": "-9",
          "choices": ["-20", "-9", "-14"]
        },
        "5": {
          "type": "select",
          "description": "",
          "question": "What is the Value of this index?",
          "answer": "-13",
          "choices": ["-24", "15", "-13"]
        },
        "6": {
          "type": "select",
          "description": "",
          "question": "What is the Value of this index?",
          "answer": "-17",
          "choices": ["-13", "-17", "-28"]
        },
        "7": {
          "type": "select",
          "description": "",
          "question": "What is the Value of this index?",
          "answer": "-21",
          "choices": ["-21", "-32", "-26"]
        },
        "8": {
          "type": "select",
          "description": "",
          "question": "What is the Value of this index?",
          "answer": "5",
          "choices": ["0", "-6", "5"]
        },
        "9": {
          "type": "select",
          "description": "",
          "question": "What is the Value of this index?",
          "answer": "1",
          "choices": ["-10", "1", "0"]
        },
        "10": {
          "type": "select",
          "description": "",
          "question": "What is the Value of this index?",
          "answer": "7",
          "choices": ["1", "0", "7"]
        },
        "11": {
          "type": "select",
          "description": "",
          "question": "What is the Value of this index?",
          "answer": "8",
          "choices": ["5", "8", "-3"]
        },
        "12": {
          "type": "select",
          "description": "",
          "question": "What is the Value of this index?",
          "answer": "4",
          "choices": ["4", "-4", "3"]
        },
        "13": {
          "type": "select",
          "description": "",
          "question": "What is the Value of this index?",
          "answer": "-13",
          "choices": ["-24", "-18", "-13"]
        },
        "14": {
          "type": "select",
          "description": "",
          "question": "What is the Value of this index?",
          "answer": "-6",
          "choices": ["-17", "-6", "-7"]
        },
        "15": {
          "type": "select",
          "description": "",
          "question": "What is the Value of this index?",
          "answer": "1",
          "choices": ["1", "-10", "-4"]
        },
        "16": {
          "type": "select",
          "description": "",
          "question": "What is the Value of this index?",
          "answer": "1",
          "choices": ["-1", "0", "1"]
        },
        "17": {
          "type": "select",
          "description": "",
          "question": "What is the Value of this index?",
          "answer": "3",
          "choices": ["2", "3", "-3"]
        },
        "18": {
          "type": "select",
          "description": "",
          "question": "What is the Value of this index?",
          "answer": "9",
          "choices": ["9", "-2", "-1"]
        }
        } 
    }
  }
  